{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Metal Carport Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40379/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40379,"taskName":"Carport (Metal) - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Metal Carport","xmTaskDescriptor":"Metal Carport Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":5119,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carport building door","textMessagingName":"Build Carport","rolloverLongDesc":"Built in a similar manner to most homes, these structures tend to be built by general contractors \u0026 result in a carport that matches the look of the rest of the home.","rolloverShortDesc":"Made with posts or columns, wood joists \u0026 roofing.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Metal Carport.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Build a Metal Carport \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Steel Carport Builders","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":37,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Build Metal Carport","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Carport (Metal) - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Metal Carport Builder Need","urlName":"Carport-Metal-Build","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Metal Carport Builders - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Carport,building,door,,,match,Metal,Build","emcCategoryOid":-12036,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":673,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40379/":{"taskOID":40379,"originalTaskOID":40379,"setID":673,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4598,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Carport","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size carport do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4368,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One car","answerDisplayText":"One car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6546,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two cars","answerDisplayText":"Two cars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2353,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Extra storage space","answerDisplayText":"Extra storage space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4484,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Carport","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want the carport installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2312,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Extension of house/building","answerDisplayText":"Extension of house/building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1898,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Detached from house/building","answerDisplayText":"Detached from house/building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1897,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Detached but connected by covered walk/breezeway","answerDisplayText":"Detached but connected by covered walk/breezeway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4601,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want included?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1580,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Concrete slab floor","answerDisplayText":"Concrete slab floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2514,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Flat roof","answerDisplayText":"Flat roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2700,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gable roof","answerDisplayText":"Gable roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3730,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Mansard roof","answerDisplayText":"Mansard roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2209,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Enclosed","answerDisplayText":"Enclosed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2892,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gutters","answerDisplayText":"Gutters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2169,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Electric lights","answerDisplayText":"Electric lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5770,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Skylights","answerDisplayText":"Skylights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2384,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Fan","answerDisplayText":"Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4598,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Carport","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size carport do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4368,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One car","answerDisplayText":"One car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6546,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two cars","answerDisplayText":"Two cars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2353,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Extra storage space","answerDisplayText":"Extra storage space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4368,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One car","answerDisplayText":"One car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6546,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two cars","answerDisplayText":"Two cars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2353,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Extra storage space","answerDisplayText":"Extra storage space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4484,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Carport","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want the carport installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2312,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Extension of house/building","answerDisplayText":"Extension of house/building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1898,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Detached from house/building","answerDisplayText":"Detached from house/building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1897,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Detached but connected by covered walk/breezeway","answerDisplayText":"Detached but connected by covered walk/breezeway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2312,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Extension of house/building","answerDisplayText":"Extension of house/building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1898,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Detached from house/building","answerDisplayText":"Detached from house/building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1897,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Detached but connected by covered walk/breezeway","answerDisplayText":"Detached but connected by covered walk/breezeway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4601,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want included?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1580,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Concrete slab floor","answerDisplayText":"Concrete slab floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2514,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Flat roof","answerDisplayText":"Flat roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2700,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gable roof","answerDisplayText":"Gable roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3730,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Mansard roof","answerDisplayText":"Mansard roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2209,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Enclosed","answerDisplayText":"Enclosed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2892,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gutters","answerDisplayText":"Gutters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2169,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Electric lights","answerDisplayText":"Electric lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5770,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Skylights","answerDisplayText":"Skylights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2384,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Fan","answerDisplayText":"Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1580,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Concrete slab floor","answerDisplayText":"Concrete slab floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2514,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Flat roof","answerDisplayText":"Flat roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2700,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gable roof","answerDisplayText":"Gable roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3730,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Mansard roof","answerDisplayText":"Mansard roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2209,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Enclosed","answerDisplayText":"Enclosed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2892,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gutters","answerDisplayText":"Gutters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2169,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Electric lights","answerDisplayText":"Electric lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5770,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Skylights","answerDisplayText":"Skylights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2384,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Fan","answerDisplayText":"Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}